<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Filtrations on Sri Bharathi Group</title>
    <link>/filtration/filtration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Filtrations on Sri Bharathi Group</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017 - 2018, Sri Bharathi Group of companies; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="/filtration/filtration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Filter Pads &amp; Papers</title>
      <link>/filtration/filtration/filterpads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/filtration/filtration/filterpads/</guid>
      <description>We offer Filter Pads in two categories namely Cellulose Pulp and Carbon Activated. Cellulose Pulp category of Filter Pad comes with varied specification to suite the final filtering process deployed at the plant.
We manufacture a wide range of filter papers &amp;amp; pads on a very highly sophisticated production plant. The entire process of manufacturing is untouched by hand from the pulping stage to the finished product. This is a high precision completely automatic plant which ensures a uniformly produced filter media for excellent purity and frees from external contaminants qualities vital for sensitive industries like drugs, pharmaceuticals, foods, beverages, chemicals, cosmetics etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filtration</title>
      <link>/filtration/filtration/filtercartridges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/filtration/filtration/filtercartridges/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>