<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Filtrations on Sri Bharathi Group</title>
    <link>/filtration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Filtrations on Sri Bharathi Group</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017 - 2018, Sri Bharathi Group of companies; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="/filtration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Filtration</title>
      <link>/filtration/filtercartridges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/filtration/filtercartridges/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filtration Pads</title>
      <link>/filtration/filterpads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/filtration/filterpads/</guid>
      <description>Apart from standard specifications, we use OnDemand approach to manufacture the products to suite custom requirements. The raw material used for the manufacturing of the Filter Pads is 100% Virgin Pulp and is unbleached. The filter pads are manufactured and continuously monitored under the rules of food act so it is food gradable.        We offer Filter Pads in two categories namely Cellulose Pulp and Carbon Activated and their details can be found under respective link.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>