<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on Sri Bharathi Group</title>
    <link>/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on Sri Bharathi Group</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017 - 2018, Sri Bharathi Group of companies; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/verticles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/verticles/</guid>
      <description>We warmly welcome you to our web portal – Sri Bharathi Group of companies.
Sri Bharathi Group of companies is established by an eminent visionary with more than 40 years of industrial deep-rooted experience and expertise keeping the outlook on the fast-flourishing technical advance which gallops incredibly beyond leaps and bounds. In industry, the prime objective is the manufacture of products with pristine purity. The consumers of today are well acquainted with quality of consumables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Core values</title>
      <link>/about/values/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/values/</guid>
      <description> Being a joint venture between Sri Bharathi Enterprises and National Card Board Mill we provide great value adds not only in terms of quality but also the professional after sales services. Highly customizable specification in terms of crucial aspects like Fiber Length, Viscosity, Moisture etc. Use On-Demand approach to tailor the product based on your need to suite your requirements on:  Shape Size / Dimension Technical Specification  Supply Filter Pads which are manufactured using:  Wood Pulp Cotton Pulp Hybrid/Mixture of Pulps  Adheres to high quality standards Competitive pricing Protected from the dollar exchange rate fluctuation Offer 24*7 support Certified for usage in Food &amp;amp; Pharmaceutical industries Offers end-to-end support which includes Water Proof Packaging, Transportation, etc  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Focus Areas</title>
      <link>/about/focusareas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/focusareas/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Strength</title>
      <link>/about/strength/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/strength/</guid>
      <description>Established by an eminent subject matter expert with more than 40 years of experience in the industry. We have tie-up with technical leaders and other organizations in the Filtering Industry. Manufacturing of High Quality Filter Pads, Filter Bags and other Industrial Filtering Equipments. Our continuous Research &amp;amp; Developments are tailored to the most recent technological up heaves. Its activities are governed by the ethical principles and garnered to the glory for its maintaining the promises and the standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sri Bharathi Group of Companies</title>
      <link>/about/company/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/company/</guid>
      <description>We warmly welcome you to our web portal Sri Bharathi Group of companies.
Sri Bharathi Group of companies is established by an eminent visionary with more than 40 years of industrial deep-rooted experience and expertise keeping the outlook on the fast-flourishing technical advance which gallops incredibly beyond leaps and bounds. In industry, the prime objective is the manufacture of products with pristine purity. The consumers of today are well acquainted with quality of consumables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standards &amp; Certifications</title>
      <link>/about/standards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/standards/</guid>
      <description> 100% secure and protected from any external adulteration/contamination We do not use any solvent / chemical and the adhere to the strict norms of Food &amp;amp; Pharmaceutical Industries Fully automated and lesser human intervention for the high quality and safety of pads ISO 9001-2000 Certified manufacturing unit Dun &amp;amp; Bradstreet Certified manufacturing unit (edited by vaidyanthan)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>